sorapedia.com 2011-12-31

# 

[Subscribe RSS](http://feeds.feedburner.com/sorapedia)» |  | [**GET UPDATES ON SMS FREE**](http://labs.google.co.in/smschannels/subscribe/sorapedia) » |  | [Subscribe By EMAIL](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=Sorapedia&loc=en_US)» |  | [READ in HINDI](http://translate.google.com/translate?hl=en&langpair=en|hi&sl=en&tl=hi&u=http://sorapedia.com/)» |  | [Guest Writer](http://sorapedia.com/contact)» | [Sitemap](http://sorapedia.com/index-php/sitemap)» | [Login](http://sorapedia.com/wp-login.php?)» |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
sorapedia.com provide information about Career , Jobs , Education and Other Related information. In general sorapedia.com does not collect Personal Information about any visitors when they visit the site. 

All viewers are visiting the site without revealing Personal Information except comment section. Sorapedia.com treat visitors privacy at most important. 

**Log Files and  Visits Traffic**

sorapedia.com records your visit and other logs  for statistical purposes like IP address;  ISP, click trends, Language, demographic details, geographic location,Browser Type in  use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded , Entrance Path, Keyword, entrance source, web address . These information are not by any mean is personally Identifiable.

We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider’s logs.

**Cookies**

A cookie (also tracking cookie, browser cookie, and HTTP cookie) is a small piece of text stored on a user's computer by a web browser. A cookie consists of one or more name-value pairs containing bits of information.

A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

sorapedia.com doesn't use cookies to store information about their visitors by any mean like visitor preferences or record any user specific data.

**Google DART Cookies**

**What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

Our site and third parties such as advertisers may add a cookie to help analyze web traffic or to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or Alternatively, you may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Subscription and Electronic Newsletter**

When You subscribe for Newsletter for daily updates, Your email address will only be recorded . It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by using the link provided in every newsletter. 

Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.

**Collection of Personal Information:**

If at any time you believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webmaster through the contact us page.

**Note:** The use of the term “Personal Information” in this privacy statement refers to any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.

**Contacting Us**

We welcome your suggestions and feedback to improve our service and request that any error found may kindly be brought to our notice.

[ **[Contact Sorapedia.com Page](mailto:admin@sorapedia.com)** ]
